The Bloody Conclusion to the 'Axis' Trilogy!
Puppet Master: Axis Termination is a fantasy, horror,
war film directed by Charles Band.
To stop the Third Reich and the Nazi war machine from winning World War II and affecting the outcome of the
free world, Toulon's indestructible puppets join forces with the masters of psychic powers.
Doctor Ivan Ivanov, played by George Appleby.
Doktor Gerde Ernst, played by Tonya Kay.
Captain Brooks, played by Paul Logan.
Steiner Krabke, played by Kevin Scott Allen.
Elisa Ivanov, played by Tania Fox.
Georgina Vale, played by Alynxia America.
Puppet Master: Axis Termination is a 2017 film directed by Charles Band.
It is the eleventh film of the Puppet Master series.
The film continues where Puppet Master X: Axis Rising left off.
It is the third and final installment of the Axis Trilogy.
The film explores themes of nazi, magic, world war ii, puppet, sequel.
The tone is dark.